(Arms down, head back, hold on!)
🎶
Take me as I am
or you can watch me as I go
🎶
Never stood a chance
Nothing more than an echo (echo)
🎶
(echo)
Ruin all my plans
Tell me things I shouldn't know
(know, know, know, know, know)
Strike me where I stand
I'll even open the window!
(window, window)
Cuz I'm over it!
I'm over it all!
I'm underwhelmed by the start of the fall
and I'm oddly comforted by the thought
that if you blink twice
then I'll be gone
Yeah, I'm over it!
I'm over it all!
If nothing is right
then everything's wrong
And I'm hardly comforted by the thought
When I'm on thin ice
I'll play along!
Take me out with the trash!
and don't dig up the past!
With each tap of the glass
feel it crack, I feel it crack!
Drag me down with the rats!
and don't dig up the scraps!
I'll cover up my tracks
Won't look back!
I won't look back!
🎶
(back, back back, hold on!)
Sinking in the sand
Now it's out of my control
🎶
Don't reach for my hand
You didn't care till I let go
LET
ME
GO!
Cuz I'm over it!
My head's in the clouds
I'm tired of regret weighing me down
and I'm so scared I won't escape the sound
Constant reminders
of all my doubts
Yeah, I'm over it!
the running around
I'm wired to swim
but I'm gonna drown
and I don't care if I don't make you proud
but I'm a liar
waiting to bow!
Take me out with the trash!
and don't dig up the past!
With each tap of the glass
feel it crack, I feel it crack!
Drag me down with the rats!
and don't dig up the scraps!
I'll cover up my tracks
Won't look back!
I won't look back!
You look me in the eyes
You tell me pretty lies
Like that'll make me try
but I've made up my mind
You look me in the eyes
and tell me pretty lies
like that'll make me try
but I've made up my mind
Stop telling me lies!
I've made up my mind!
Leave me behind!
Take me out with the trash!
and don't dig up the past!
With each tap of the glass
feel it crack, I feel it crack!
Drag me down with the rats!
and don't dig up the scraps!
I'll cover up my tracks
Won't look back!
I won't look back!
🎶
(you look me in the eyes)
(and you tell me pretty lies)
(like that'll make me try)
(back, back, back, hold on!)
🎶